Riders, you know what time it is when the bike starts screaming.
骑手们，当车子开始嘶吼的时候，你就知道时候到了。
Yep, you don't stay in the same gear, you kick it up a notch.
没错，你不会一直待在同一个档位，你会往上加一档。
And that's exactly the idea behind Verified Boost Rider.
而这正是认证加速骑手背后的想法。
And yes, DirtBikeX is always the real home to free riders, and the verified boost rider is for the people who want the next layer, the flair, the stats, the custom invites, and the insider hacks.
而且没错，DirtBikeX 永远是自由骑手真正的家，而认证加速骑手是给那些想要更上一层的人准备的：标识、数据、自定义邀请，还有内部技巧。
Once you get the membership, you can go ahead and go to Profile Edit and set up your custom flair so others know you're verified
拿到会员资格之后，你就可以去个人资料的编辑页，设置你的自定义标识，让别人知道你已认证
You can bring fellow riders in with stronger invite tools, your custom invite code, and you get to see who actually accepted.
你可以用更强的邀请工具把车友带进来，用你的自定义邀请码，而且你能看到谁真正接受了。
And if you hold a sponsorship pass, you get deeper stats.
而如果你持有赞助通行证，你会得到更深入的数据。
Previous months, faster updates, and more insight into who actually engaged with your spot.
之前的月份、更快的更新，以及更深入地了解谁真正和你的场地互动过。
Boost Rider also get a special group chat, early updates, and features I'm testing with the community first.
加速骑手还能拿到专属群聊、更早的更新，以及我优先和社区一起测试的功能。
So no, you don't need this to enjoy the community, but if you want to be part of what I'm building,
所以不，你不需要这个也能享受这个社区，但如果你想成为我正在打造的东西的一部分，
I can guarantee you this will help shape it.
我可以向你保证，这会帮助塑造它。
My name is Rubio, and if you want to become one, follow and go check out my link in
我叫鲁比奥，如果你想成为其中一员，点个关注，链接就在我
the bio.
主页简介里。